No. When I eat Froot Loops,
the other astronauts make fun of me!
I don't wanna wait
until you're back to get married.
(Howard:)What?
l wanna be married to you
before you get in that rocket.
(Howard:)But I'm leaving in two days.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)What about Apple Jacks?
I don't need to take cereal!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)What kind of breakfast do you think...
...they're gonna give you in Russia?
(Howard:)They invented
the light bulb in New Jersey!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)It doesn't mean they hand them out
to you when you go!
We'll have a little ceremony
with just our friends.
(Bernadette:)We'll still have the big reception
with everyone when you get back.
(Howard:)Wow, okay, let's get married.
You know what?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)I'll buy you All-Bran in case
you get stopped up in outer space!